[{"question_type": "single",
  "question": "A Python object is most similar to a ____.",
  "answers": ["noun"],
  "incorrect": ["verb", "adjective", "union"],
  "category": "objects",
  "difficulty": 0,
  "uuid": "e85975b7-44e1-4b68-96f1-b98f0e24a7f0"},

  {"question_type": "multiple",
    "question": "Select the built-in object types:",
    "answers": ["int", "str", "list", "set"],
    "incorrect": ["vec", "vector", "double"],
    "category": "objects",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "uuid": "cd9b537d-fe0a-4831-8202-dfcf55df1dcc"},

  {"question_type": "numerical",
    "question": "What is the the value of c: \\na=5\\nb=2\\nc=a**b",
    "answers": [25],
    "incorrect": [],
    "category": "operators",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "uuid": "c9cffe01-a7f5-41b7-8279-6d0359fa1d4b"},

  {"question_type": "single",
    "question": "The ____ object is not mutable.",
    "answers": ["tuple"],
    "incorrect": ["list", "set", "dict"],
    "category": "objects",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "uuid": "94dcf13d-a089-480c-a1f3-6e2fc7bab6db"},

  {"question_type": "single",
    "question": "[1, 2, 3] is a ____",
    "answers": ["list"],
    "incorrect": ["set", "dict", "vec", "int"],
    "category": "objects",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "uuid": "1c4fa613-9d6d-47f9-868f-8d7ffbcdfc11"},

  {"question_type": "single",
    "question": "{\'a\', \'b\', \'c\', \'d\'} is a ____",
    "answers": ["set"],
    "incorrect": ["list", "dict", "vec", "str"],
    "category": "objects",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "uuid": "35828ecf-8f17-44f7-8e35-63a4c846774d"},

  {"question_type": "single",
    "question": "{\'a\': 1, \'b\': 1, \'c\': 2, \'d\': 5} is a ____",
    "answers": ["dict"],
    "incorrect": ["list", "hash", "vec", "keyval"],
    "category": "objects",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "uuid": "ada82b0d-debb-4b5e-8b58-469595ecfe79"},

  {"question_type": "single",
    "question": "____ is not a Python keyword.",
    "answers": ["foreach"],
    "incorrect": ["in", "and", "type", "None"],
    "category": "misc",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "uuid": "9f9be79d-e108-4174-9ce6-fe37efebcad8"},

  {"question_type": "single",
    "question": "Dictionary keys must be ____",
    "answers": ["immutable"],
    "incorrect": ["integers", "builtins", "incrementing"],
    "category": "objects",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "uuid": "1a0529eb-6d4c-4108-bb69-fc820046f679"},

  {"question_type": "single",
    "question": "To define a new object class, Python uses the ____ keyword.",
    "answers": ["class"],
    "incorrect": ["def", "cls", "fn", "object"],
    "category": "objects",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "uuid": "0599f10e-2699-4d52-8287-3912ebec5f68"},

  {"question_type": "single",
    "question": "Under the covers, the len funcion calls ____.",
    "answers": ["__len__"],
    "incorrect": ["__size__", "__shape__", "__length", "index[-1]"],
    "category": "objects",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "uuid": "b420f8ec-2645-42ef-b1d0-4506333cc34b"},

  {"question_type": "single",
    "question": "Under the covers, the len funcion calls ____.",
    "answers": ["__len__"],
    "incorrect": ["__size__", "__shape__", "__length", "index[-1]"],
    "category": "objects",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "uuid": "10799038-901f-45fe-906b-b37187956b16"},

  {"question_type": "single",
    "question": "To handle errors, Python uses _____",
    "answers": ["try/except"],
    "incorrect": ["try/catch", "if/else", "do/except", "do/catch"],
    "category": "objects",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "uuid": "b82e87f8-3a0b-4c7d-9480-a08f82029190"}]